One second before despair, the stars shine faintly Because I love you
I get anxious in the middle of an intersection
Hello. I'm Iroha Okuda, a 465th member of Nogizaka.
I'm Iroha Okuda, a member of Nogizaka's 465th term.
You can't see me, but I'm at Kashiwa Station.
What's the reason I'm here? I'm here to do a street performance.
Wow, you know...
I'm nervous because there are more people than I expected.
I thought it would be nerve-wracking for the audience as well as the performer.
I wrote that only those who come close to me can see me.
So I'm going to get ready and do my best to sing.
There are a lot of people here.
What should I do?
I don't know. I've never been at home.
I've only played guitar in front of my fans.
I feel like I'm completely away from home.
That's why I'm scared. I'm away.
I've only sung for people who know me.
I wonder if it's okay to sing here.
I'm afraid they'll think, "What the hell is this guy doing here?
Okay.
I'm getting nervous.
I'm so nervous.
I'll ask him.
Okay.
Tell me how you feel looking at yourself
Lately I've been spinning and breaking
When did the wind start blowing When did the wind start blowing
Emotional wings don't stop twirling, they're bothering me.
My mind is buzzing
I'm worried about that cloud that's covering me
That's because I don't believe in tomorrow
What do you think about yourself
One second before electromagnetic despair
The stars are shining faintly
Can you see the darkness coming here?
I found my dream
In a planet full of planets
I am searching for my only dream
Who's to blame, I go along without responsibility
Waiting for the dawn sky that never comes
I ask you what you want to do with yourself in the end
Looking at yourself
What do you see there?
Look at yourself
I am searching for my only dream
Can you see the darkness coming here?
I am searching for my only dream I am searching for my only dream
I am searching for my only dream
Can you see the darkness coming here?
Amongst a planet full of
I have lost my way
I am searching for my only dream
I go along without responsibility for whose fault it is
Waiting for the dawn sky that will never come
I ask you what you want to do with yourself in the end
I am searching for my only dream
thank you so much
I am happy
Thank you for watching
The town I saw from the train window was so far away.
Has the person I've longed for moved away already?
Has the promise we made that day been forgotten?
No one is listening to a single word
The glamorous showbiz I saw in a magazine
Have they been stained by the marks of someone's hands that were peeping at them
I think it's more unfortunate than giving up
Is more unfortunate than giving up
Knowing both the dream and the reality
While being able to talk about it comfortably Be at ease with the easy talk
Life is to live strong
Since when do we not shed a tear
We may be young
We're not stronger than we were then
Even when we grow up, we still have sadness in our hearts
We hold it in by combing the bamboo and the leaves
But it's okay to cry once in a while
When we find our dream
We'll find our dream
When did we stop crying?
We're not stronger than when we were young
Even when we grow up, there are still sad things
We clench our bamboos and leaves to hold it together
But it's okay to cry once in a while
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy! A lot! Thank you so much!
I'm glad you're home from work.
Thank you for coming.
I'm so happy. I didn't think anyone would stop for me.
I'm so glad.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
Music.
Let's get off at the next stop and walk through the city at dusk.
Through the crowds of the shopping arcade
Alone on the road to my house
With the wind blowing in the breeze
I'll think about today I'll think about today.
I need some time.
It's a very important choice for both of us right now.
It's not an easy decision to make.
Because I love you.
I'll look you in the eye as I come to any conclusion
I'd like to answer you with a roundabout way of loving you
If you could hold me in your arms
I'll walk on my own two feet
I'll walk step by step
Everything is a history of love
All is a history of love
I just need more time.
It's a very important choice for both of us right now
It's not an easy decision to make
Because I love you.
Whatever the conclusion, I want to look you in the eye.
I want to answer you... with a roundabout way of loving you.
Mmm.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad you knew.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
I'm not even 17 years old... but I'm a little old for high school... and now here's a motherly bone...
Thank you so much!
I'm a college student, I'm 23 years old and I'm still an adult.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for stopping by, even though we're all going through a hard time.Thank you very much for stopping by, even though it's not easy for everyone.
Oh, wow!
This is really my first time to do a live performance on the street, so I'm not very good at it.
Thank you very much for watching.
My seat was in the back, so it was hard for everyone to see me.
But I didn't give up. I smiled like myself.
The fact that such a flower kept blooming is a miracle.
The many people I will meet from now on will fill my memory.
I hope they will never forget me or you.
I hope they don't forget about me.
The many people I'll meet from now on will flood my memory
I hope they don't forget me and you
I hope you don't forget me
I hope you never forget.
Thank you very much.
Great. The next one will be my last.
Let's tune in for a bit.
Ei-chan is tuning up and chatting.
Have you ever been to a Nogizaka concert?
Yes, have you? Who is your favorite?
Mr. Nioki
Oh, Mao!
I'm sorry if this is not Cafe Au Lait, but...
I'm sorry I'm the only one.
I hope you like me too!
That's great.
Have you been to any of the other Kizaka concerts?
Did you? When did you come?
The last one was quite a while ago.
The last one was my brother. Finally, brothers.
Brothers?
They look like each other.
I've been running.
Thank you very much.
Who do you prefer?
I've always been with Na-chan.
Is that so? Then put this on.
I think it's fate that we met here.
I hope you'll like it and go home.
I'm so happy! Who's your favorite?
Lenka.
Mr. Lenka!
I love Lenka too!
That's...
I see.
Well, you and your brother should come see me sometime.
I'll be there.
That's so nice of you.
Thank you very much.
I'll play the last song.
Music.
I wonder how long that light will stay green.
It suddenly starts blinking, like it's rushing me.
Before I know it, I'm walking a little faster
As if it doesn't matter what I want.
Everyone is running at the same time, everyone is running at the same time.
What is it that they're in such a hurry to catch up with?
I'm looking at this objectively. I hate it. I'm being objective. I don't like me.
It's not logic that triggers a light heart.
It always starts with this impulse in my heart.
To be swept away... is to resist.
To live is to choose only one option.
Look, in the crowd, someone starts running.
Like a hook, they all start to run.
I start running.
I can't decide for myself, and I need something to push me forward.
A trigger.
It's not logic that triggers my light heart, it's always the impulse in my heart.
To be swept away, to resist, to live is to choose only one option.
Lightness of heart comes from me
Let's live as we are
Words, music, arrangement by Miho Nakajima
Sung by Miho Nakajima
Sung by Miho Nakashima
Miho Nakashima
Singing Miho Nakashima
Thank you very much.
Amazing.
It was my first time to do a live performance on the street.
I'm glad you were all there.
Thank you very much.
Bye.
Please leave with at least a name.
I'm Iroha Okuda.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Yay.
Thank you very much.
It was my first time performing on the street.
I wasn't sure how it would go.
In terms of singing and guitar.
I gave it about a 65.
I hope to be able to do it again sometime in the future.
But it was my first time
It was my first time to perform in a place I didn't know.
I had a chance to meet some people who knew me
who happened to know me.
And...
I don't know.
I don't know, but they stopped and listened to me
That's amazing.
This is the only way to get it.
I don't know.
It's so special
I feel so special
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
It was fun to talk to people I've never met before.
See you soon!
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating
Thank you very much for subscribing and rating my channel!
See you soon! See you soon.
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.